Sup, [__] I see you.
How do I see how many [__] are
watching? Oh, damn. I didn't expect this
many people right away. Press one if you
can hear my ass.
Press one if you can hear my ass. Sup.
Oh, damn. Hold up. I got I I gotta go I
got to go open up my phone and like turn
somehow.
Hold on. I've never done this before.
So, this is a new experience, [__]
Hold up.
Okay, we good. I just opened up my chat
on my phone, so now I can see in real
time.
Thanks, Tony. The talking clock. It I
don't know if it's a PNG. I think it's
more of a V2 or some [__] I don't know.
I don't give a [__] I spent $2,000 on
it, though. I ain't never getting his
money back.
Uh, completely false is right. Yeah,
like I'm not even kidding. This looks
exactly like how I look in real life.
Like people who saw me like wear my coba
boxes, they'll know that the cowboy box
is like, you know, like based off of
like how I actually look and [__] And
and the dollar like look at this. Hold
on. I can like hold on, hold on,
[__] I can like put the dollar away
whenever I want. Like look at that.
Oh my god. That cost that alone that
cost me like 150 bucks. The arm toggle.
Like I am not even kidding. Although
like I I like it because it like it
shows how much money I've got.
And as you can see like down here I've
also got like a bunch of dollar bills.
[__] You know, you see they're like all
$100 bills because I need to really
accentuate how much money I've got and
[__] like because it's like I'm rich and
[__]
Hold on, [__] I'm trying to figure
out how to see how many people are in
the stream because I can't tell [__] I
do not understand how this how any of
these menus work.
Tiffany, you should you show up and play
the game. How? Okay. Okay, I see.
There's like 95 [__] watching. Damn.
I expected like maybe two or three at
max.
How am I rich? Because I because I
because I make videos on YouTube. You
know, you know this [__]
Hold on. What? YouTube is not receiving
enough video to maintain smooth
streaming. What does that mean? I I
don't know.
Anyways, [__] like I decided to pick
this game because it's like it's simple
and [__] and like all I really got to do
is walk around.
What do you mean there's lag? Lemon
gaze, what do you mean there's lag? I am
not get experiencing any lag of mine.
Hold on, [__] There is lag.
What do you guys mean? There's lag. I'm
not getting any lag on mine.
Kgate cake goals. This game might be too
scary for you. Shut you. Shut up,
[__] I live through when Sonic
Unground was cancelled. Like, I I've
been through scary [__]
See, that's what I'm taking. That's what
I'm saying. Alan Carlson or whatever the
[__] your name is. I don't see any lag
either. Please, please play Danny's
World. I'm planning on doing that.
Hold on, [__] Give me like just like
two minutes. I'm like messing around
with the settings to fix the lag and
[__] as if I know what I'm doing.
Okay. Press one if the stream is is
running fine. Press two if it's laggy as
[__]
Okay. Damn, I'm seeing a lot of ones in
the chat. So, like I think all you
[__] saying two, I think that's on
your end. I don't I don't know what to
tell you. I'm going to start the game.
There's like 80 [__] here and we'll
just we're just jumping. Who? Who? May
the weirdo. Who the What do you mean by
three? Uh-uh. No. No. Alan Carlson. No.
I don't want to kick you from the chat.
We're not doing the 67 [__] up in here.
Okay, let's go ahead and begin the game.
And just so you guys know, I I don't do
scary [__] Like I I I just don't. So,
it's Halloween night and you've got the
house to yourself. Your grandmother had
a sudden injury and your parents thought
it was best to spend the night with her
just to be safe. As you're 14 now, your
parents kept you home for the night to
match the trick-or-treaters.
Just after your parents left home, you
bought a small box of candy and prepared
for the evening. They should only be
gone for the night and everything should
run smoothly.
Okay, [__] lock in because I have no
idea what's what's going to happen up in
this [__]
Pick up.
Who is calling me? My mama. Okay. Um,
hey mama. Okay, honey. We'll be at
grandma's overnight. Okay. Okay. Doctor
said there's nothing to worry about, but
suggested that we stay with her for the
night. Mama, grandma's dying.
Where? Oh, no. Yeah, I got the candy, by
the way. It better be like Reese's
Pieces or some [__] Oh, good. Just
remember to clean the yard at the kids
leave. I ain't doing that. I ain't doing
that. You know how it gets. Yeah. Okay,
whatever, Mom. Also, the neighborhood
across the street said he'd keep an eye
on the H. That's kind of creepy. My
neighbor. You know how he's late? How
how late he's awake?
Oh, he better not be on the registry.
Really, Mom? You know I don't like the
neighbor. He creeps me out. He's on the
registry.
Relax. He'll keep watch from his house.
You'll probably be sleeping anyway. All
right. Love you.
Oh, and don't freak yourself out if you
hear anything strange downstairs. That
old water pop has been acting up
recently. Oh, hell no. It seems it
sometimes makes some struggling noises.
If it stirs up, just go downstairs and
give it a smack. That should simply stop
the noise. I'm not doing that. Uh-uh.
You got to be booping on my butt if you
think I'm doing that. Love you, mama.
Love you.
That's why I'm saying Moonflow for life.
He's a predator. I don't want to be
dealing with this. It's Halloween. I
want candy.
Oh my god, why am I so short? I cannot
be 14 years old. What? Seems to be
getting late. I should probably get set
up. The candy for the ball should be in
my bedroom if I remember correctly.
Oh, no. No. Oh, okay. I I'm taller than
I thought. I thought I was a [__] or
some [__]
Do midgetes have like normal houses or
is like everything is slightly smaller?
Oh, this house is big. Oh my. How rich
are we?
How rich is my mama?
We've got lights on the ceilings and
under the cabinets. We got hanging
lights. We got candles, too. A house
don't need this many lights. This is
like three houses in one. I'm rich. Oh,
it's dark in there. I don't like that. I
don't like that one bit.
What's over here?
Oh, nu. I'm not doing that. You got to
be pooping on my butt if you think I'm
doing that. I'm not going down there.
I gota look outside the neighbor to make
sure the the We got a picket fence.
That's how we That's how you know we
made it. We made out of the hood, mama.
Damn. I I don't see any creepy neighbors
outside.
Damn. This guy is blood red. This is
scary. Oh my What? Okay, mama ain't
home. I can walk wherever I want. Where
did I find the candy? Didn't they say
it's upstairs?
Is this my room?
This game is hard. Where is the candy?
What is that?
Damn. It's like one of those little fish
things, like fish lots or some [__] I
don't know. I don't give a [__] Where
is the candy? Oh, it better not be in
there.
Uh-uh.
Do
we're gonna be using this. We're going
to be using this room all night. I'm
calling it. God damn. Do I go going in
the dark? What if the neighbor is in my
house?
Where is the candy? I don't see
anything. Where is the candy?
Didn't they see? Okay. Is Oh, wait. Is
that on the ground?
I expected some Snickers or some [__]
What is this?
I cannot even tell what that is. That is
some grandma candy up in this [__] Oh
my god. Do I just take it outside? Oh,
here's the ball.
Throw it in the ball.
Nothing too good this year. Just some
small candies.
Will they were good enough for me to eat
half the box? I'm I'm canonically fat.
Okay. Hey, I I hope the kids don't mind.
I have like watch some watching some TV
while I wait for the night to start out.
Shouldn't be too long now.
I am scared the neighbor is just going
to break into my goddamn house and
assault me.
I mean, canonically, I'm a fat [__] I
bet I could fat back if I wanted to.
Where's the TV? It said something about
like watching TV.
Is it over here? Oh, there it is.
What do you mean, Sarah? What do you
mean the lag? People are saying that
there's not lag. Are you stupid?
Hell yeah, Javier. I think Javier M812.
Oh, those strawberry candies are all the
[__] [__] I love that [__] I love
it.
What am I watching?
Sounds like trick or treat are here.
Much later than expected.
Maybe a short night after all. Well, I
better answer the goddamn door.
Who is it? What do you want? It's too
late for candy. Oh, damn. That is that
is Yeah. Yeah, that looks like a kid.
Oh. Oh, [__]
Hey [__] you want this candy? Straight
trickor treat now.
Are you gonna take the candy? Happy
Halloween.
What a great costume. How do you imagine
get that on your head?
Just give me the candy. I'm too old for
this [__] Y'all never too old for
trick-or-treating. You just got to take
a trick or treat.
How many can I give him?
Oh [__]
Can I break the game?
Here, I'll give you one so you can go
away. I I I was watching what the hell
was on TV.
How many of these [__] can I make?
Should I just go back and watch TV now?
Can I eat the can? Damn, I can do the
file.
Just Just got to make sure there's no
like creepy peaches. Oh [__] somebody's
at the door again already. What do you
want? What do you want? Another another
[__] kid. Oh damn,
you're kind of creepier than the last
one. Trick or treat. And he's using
trick or treat. That's what I'm talking
about, [__] What a great costume.
Quite scary, actually. I don't know
about that. I'll grab your candy.
Thanks. Hey, he said trick or treat, so
I'll give him like two pieces of candy
at least. Boom. Oh, never mind. He's
gone.
Bye. Thank you.
What's outside?
Oh my god. What did this 14-year-old do?
Did I kidnap some [__]
Oh [__]
What do you want?
Happy Halloween. Gray costume. What a
scary skeleton, [__] I am the skeleton
from your nightmare. If this skeleton
gets good candy, he will no longer haunt
your dreams.
Okay, I'll I'll grab your candy.
Boom. Is this whole game just just
giving [__] candy? Damn.
I need to go back over to my tunes. I
got watch TV. I got to watch TV until
the neighbor gets you to beat my [__]
ass.
Don't Don't do that. Don't call the
clown clown guy hot. That is a child. I
don't want to ban you. Banan you from
this game forever.
Who is that?
Oh, that is an adult. That is an adult.
I do not want to let him answer the
door. What do you want? Take the Kenny
go. Oh, damn. I hit him balls. Hold on.
Boom. Damn. I missed. What do you want?
Have you seen my younger brother? He
forced me to put on the skull mask.
He is already intrigued with skeletons.
Not too sure why. I don't know. Oh, he
also has school mask on if you hadn't
noticed already. I I just saw him. Yeah,
he just came by. He says something
haunting my dreams. Damn. Why has he
gotten into him lately? Well, if you
have some candy, I wouldn't mind a
piece.
I mean, I guess I'll give him one. I
don't give a [__] It's at least I
deserve after watching on my brother.
Yeah, I get that. I'll give you one.
I really hope the neighborhood the
neighbor the creepy neighbor dude on the
red team. I really hope he didn't just
take this guy's brother. That That would
be the plot of the century right there.
Oh my god.
Should I just go go back and watch TV?
What do I do? I'm going to look around
my house.
What is in here?
Oh, that's Oh, another bathroom.
Damn. I let out a fat one. Oh my god. Oh
[__] He heard he heard me [__] it.
He sh He He just heard me [__] I
was hitting so I didn't even hear him
knocking.
Oh, D. What do you want? Hey you. Happy
Halloween.
What is Pooie costume? Oh, I'm I'm I'm a
ghost. I'm a ghost. I see that. Would
you like some candy, [__]
Yes.
Okay.
I I'll finally Oh my god. Trick or
treat. Finally, a [__] knows how it
works. Will you like some candy? Yes.
Coming right. I like him. I like him.
He's like a [__] like me. I respect
that. Take your candy and go. Yeah. I
Hold on.
Whoever is coming in next, they are
getting a special piece, can't they?
Hold on
there. Hold on.
Hold. Where did the candy go? Where'd it
go? I just threw it. Hold on.
There it is. Okay. Who's getting this
one? This is a special one. OH MY GOD.
OH, HELL NO. [__] I don't want to do I
don't want to give him candy. I don't
care if I drive by the toilet. Who? Who?
Who are you? Is that the neighbor? I
don't want to deal with him. Do I got Do
I got to?
He's not going to go away, is he?
Should I just
thanks A3 TV vine or whatever your name
is. I like Bobby too. I love Bonic.
Yeah. Yeah, that's what I'm doing.
Completely flaws. I I I'm just hoping he
leaves.
He ain't leaving. I'm giving the poopy
candy.
Open up.
Happy how. Whoa, that costume is
awesome. I mean, can I I would I would
think my character doesn't think it's
awesome, but I I guess we're role
playing. We're lobbying up in this
[__] Thank you. I'm going to describe
myself as a Halloween enthusiast. Oh, I
just threw the poopy candy. [__] I'm
I'm not giving to him. I take great
pride in my attire. Each I produce
something different this year. I chose a
crown. Oh, that's generic as [__] but
okay. Well, you did a great job. Even
the way you move is quite creepy. Will I
try my best? Why does it say kid? That
is not a kid. He's taller than me. Are
you kidding me? Here, just take your
candy and go. Get Get away. Uh-uh. No.
Even the way he want runs is creepy. I'm
not dealing that with that. Uh-uh.
Who is coming next?
Hello.
Oh my god. Another person. Another grown
man. This is just a man in a suit.
This man is like 56.
Happy Halloween. Gray costume. I've
always been SCARED OF VAMPIRES. WHY is
it saying kid? This is a 60 year old
man.
Why is a man coming to my house for
candy on Halloween?
Like 50. Just hand over the candy.
I mean, okay,
that was weird. He was even worse than
the clown. At least the other guy, At
least the clown,
At least he like put on a costume. That
was a man who stopped by after work. Are
you kidding me? It's going to be another
grown ass adult, isn't it?
Oh, no. This a child.
Happy Halloween, kid. Kid, that's what I
like to see. No, not in the way the
neighbor like to see kids, but you know
what I mean. Wait, there's candy here,
too? Um, yeah, of course. This place is
a jackpot. I know, [__] I know. I'm
giving out the good [__] What are you
talking about? Your dad or grandfather
is just outside your backyard.
He's giving out fullsize chocolate bar.
My daddy? Uh-uh. That's my business.
Giving out the fullsize candy bars. My
daddy is is stepping up on my turf.
Fullsized.
My parents are not home.
Wait,
wait. No, my mama's with my grandma. My
My grandma's done. Who was in my
backyard?
Just hand over the candy. Round two.
Um, should I should I go back?
Hold on. You wait there.
How do I go back? Is this my backyard?
What?
Oh, okay. I guess we're good now.
Okay. Just get get off my lawn and go.
I don't know what that was about.
Hold on. I need to look outside.
It's somebody. What the?
WHAT?
OH MY GOD. WHAT THE [__] THAT ACTUALLY
got my ass. What the? Uh-uh. Get away.
What was that?
Uh. Uh-uh.
No. Nuh-uh.
Is he going to leave? Do Do I need to
give him candy? What was that?
Hold on.
Hold on. Maybe if I give him candy,
he'll go away.
Go. Get off my lawn.
Uh-uh. He's
ain't no way he's giving the good [__]
Can I take this inside?
I know that's not my dad. Uh, get away.
I need to go in my house. Go away.
Oh my god.
What am I watching? Is California.
Is he going to leave?
What is this?
Uh, do I just go upstairs?
Cuz I I don't know what to do.
Hold on. Do Do Does Does Mama got a gun
somewhere in the house that I can use?
How do I get him out of my backyard?
What do I do?
I do not want to go in the basement. Do
I got to go in the basement?
Okay, there is nothing going on down
here. I think I think I'm good. At least
in the basement.
Oh [__] I locked myself in.
Talk to him. Okay,
hold on. I I could talk to him. I didn't
notice.
Oh, yeah. I'm I'm stupid.
What are you doing here? You scared the
life out of me. Please leave. Get out.
Get off my Get off my lawn. Relax there,
kiddo. I am 14. I am a minor. I'm just
wearing the Halloween spirit. Remember
when houses used to give out the good?
Yeah, I just saw all the good stuff.
[__] I This is my turf. I'm the one
who's supposed to be giving out the full
size stuff. You think you're hot [__]
You want one? I I I honestly do. But no,
you need to get on my prop. You I love
how I'm a 14-year-old kid killing this
like grown ass man to get off my
property. My mama will be proud. Who
said you could just sit up on our lawn,
right? We'll know how I'm done.
I'm taking this candy and you and you're
getting away.
Damn,
this neighborhood is crazy. What does
that old man think he's doing here? And
why my property? I should probably call
mama and give her a heads up.
Hey, mama. You know the creepy neighbor?
I told you. I told you not to leave me
alone with him. I told you.
[__]
Things never go right for me in this
house. All cuz I'm a [__] Hey honey,
is everything all right? Let me guess.
You ate all the candy and ran out. No,
mom.
But something odd happened. What
happened? Well, some old guy was up in
my backyard giving out large candy to
kids. He wasn't dressed up either. He
was just willing casual clothes.
When I went out to confront him, he
didn't say anything and just left. And
he even left a setup on our lawn. That
is weird. You know what? You shouldn't
have to worry too much. He's probably
just some lonely guy. Mama,
if he He did threaten me. He ran He He
ran up in my face. He's not fine. Mama.
Mama.
Oh my god.
She's been like this ever since I was
born. A [__]
Oh my god. It's Halloween for goodness
sake. People get odd.
All right. Thanks, Mom. Just uh check
in. No problem, honey. If anything else
happens, don't hesitate to call me.
Okay. Love you, Mom. Love you, too.
Damn. Things never go right for me.
I'm 14 and somehow I'm the mature one of
this house.
I do. Grim Grim Toadingo. What child
toxic this? I do.
Oh my god.
What am I watching?
Well, nobody is coming in the longest
while I think the night has ended. Or at
least I hope so.
I'm moming something about the front
line. Oh, yeah. I got to go pick up
rappers. So,
I think it's best I get that done now.
Honestly, why would I go outside after
all that?
What is that? What am I watching?
What is this?
I don't know. I You know what?
Mama ain't taking care of the house.
Grandma's dead or dying.
I'm the only one who who needs to step
up now. And and and I got to clean. It's
that simple. I got to clean [__]
Are you kidding me? I I Mama is putting
my ass to work.
Why do I have like dead bodies outside?
That's crazy.
That's strange. The old man setup is no
longer here. I mean, he's good. I mean,
it's good that he's gone. He must have
quietly backed up.
He better not be in the house.
Hold on. I think that's all I I should
throw this away.
I'm closing my house. I can't Hold on. I
I'm closing the door.
How do I throw this away? The trash
can's not there. Should I just throw it?
That's not working. Maybe I can just
throw it away in the house.
I'm closing the yard behind me. I don't
I don't trust this neighborhood.
Everybody is a freak. Everybody.
I'm paranoid, chat. Oh my god. I am
scared he is going to come out any
minute. Oh, there's a trash can. Boom.
Job well done.
Got to make sure everything's locked up
nice and tight.
I'm feeling quite hungry. There's some
leftover pizza in the fridge from last
night. I think that could work. I'll
have to warm it up in the oven.
I mean, I just ate ate like half a bag
of candy, but yeah, I could go for more
pizza.
Pizza.
Whoa.
Hell yeah.
We eating good in time.
Is it done? How do I know when it's
done?
What do you mean the door open? What do
you mean? What do you mean? Somebody
said the door opened. What door?
I think you're imagining things. I I
don't think any door opened.
The back door or the front door?
[__] I don't know what you saw. I
don't know what you saw, but
everything's closed. I think at least
for now, we're good. I I just got to go
go get my pizza and relax up in this
[__]
All right, look at that. That is some
good [__] right there. I often eat on
the couch. Well, at least when my
parents are gone.
Oh, my mama's abusive. Oh my god.
Damn. She doesn't like me eat on the
couch.
I could have eat the pizza.
That is weird.
How long is does it take to eat a pizza?
Why is it shrinking? What is going on?
That This is some This is some What am I
watching?
This is the craziest eating mechanics I
have ever ever experienced in the game.
What What is this?
He my All I'm saying is my neighbor
better not be watching my ass through
through the windows. That would be kind
of weird.
Okay. I feel like Magneto and like
somehow I'm shrinking the pizza. Like I
don't know if Magneto can do that, but
like I feel like I'm like holding my
hand to the pizza is like shrinking. And
I just think that's really funny.
That was mid. It had a strange
aftertaste.
What did my neighbor do to my pizza?
It's not that late, but I can hardly
keep my eyes open. I should head
upstairs and get changed. I keep my
pajamas in the bedroom closet.
Okay.
Not night everybody. I'm going to bed.
Not old man who is may or may not be in
my house. I'm I'm going to bed.
Time for bed. Hopefully my parents
arrive early tomorrow.
You know, I'm calling to my parents, but
I think the game only ever refers to
like my mama. So, it's like I don't know
how many parents I've got.
I'm going to be down one one
grandparent, too, with my grandma
kicking the bucket soon. And hopefully,
I'll be able to buy an even bigger house
cuz And when I say when I say me, I mean
me because my obviously my mom, she
doesn't doesn't take care of the house
the way I do. I'm scared.
Why? What's What's going to happen? Why
am I in bed?
Oh, that must be the water pump in the
basement.
Oh no. Oh no. I do not want to go in the
I better go check it out.
Man, that piece of junk.
Oh no. I'm going to have to go to the
basement owner.
Oh my god. Yes. Yes. Shivery. Like this
is me. bottle me. I've got money.
Hold on. What in the cinnamon toast?
What are you talking about?
Okay, let's let's go.
Why am I walking so slow?
You know what? Lock in everybody. We are
going straight to the basement. I'm not
even going to turn the camera because I
know I know some crazy [__] is about to
pop out.
candy. Oh no. Oh, the fourth house candy
bar.
Oh no. Oh, he is here. He is in my
house.
Oh [__]
Oh, it's over. It's over, [__]
I think I fixed it. Well, at least for
now.
Of course, this happened when I was just
beginning when I when I just began to
fall asleep.
Oh, hell no, [__] Oh, hell no. I
should go back to bed. Oh, hell no. I
can I at least take the candy with me so
I have something to snack on? No.
Oh, hell no.
Oh no.
Oh no. Oh my Oh my god.
It's over.
It's over. Tony the talking clock. You
You got spot on. It's over. We are
cooked. We are cooked. Even Did I just
see something?
I swear to you, I just saw something
move over there.
Oh, it might have just been the plant.
Okay, I'm going I'm I'm closing the
door. I've got a lock.
I've got a lock, but I'm 14. Am I smart
enough to lock it behind me? Probably
not.
Can that old man climb the house?
Probably.
How do I get in bed?
Oh, wait. Am I not supposed to go in
bed?
I I'm closing that.
I did I did leave that open, didn't I?
I hope I did.
Actually, wait. I need to go over here
and make sure the back door shut.
That is shut, right?
[__] I'm scared. But I cannot do
this [__] Okay, this place is good. I'm
going to the kitchen.
Old man, if you're here, I did not mean
to call you
a creep.
You may or may not be on the registry,
but that does not make you a bad person
right now.
It It means you were probably a bad
person once, but right now we could be
friends.
Actually, no. No, I don't want to be
friends. That That was weird. I'm taking
that back.
Oh my.
Uh, give it back. I know you took it.
Whoa. What are you talking about, kid?
You took my candy. You snatched it and
ran inside your house. That's what was
in the basement. I saw you just now.
Listen, kid. I have no idea what you're
talking about. I just got up from bed.
I'm 14.
You mean to tell me he saw the old man
run in my house and now he's looking at
me and he thinks me and him are the
same? I do not look that old. Why you
have to say it's almost midnight? Get
Get back home, kid. You're seeing
things.
Um,
what did that kid think he was doing?
Ringing doorbells at night. And why was
he still awake? I mean, what am I doing
awake either? Whatever. I I I just got
to get to bed.
Okay, maybe this neighborhood is just
like having a gas leak or some [__] and
like everybody's like kind of crazy
because like I don't know how we could
look at if that guy did run into my
house. I don't know how how he sees me a
14-y old boy and thinks, "Oh, that's the
guy who stole my candy, bitch." Uh-uh.
The kid looks like a 30 25 year old
dude. I know. I know he did. Joe 38548.
My throat, it's so dry.
I can't sleep. Oh my god. Go to bed.
It's Halloween. I need some water. There
should be some in the fridge downstairs.
[__]
This kid will not just go to bed.
Honestly, at this point, I should just
stay up. Mama's going to be home
tomorrow, probably with news that
grandma, dad,
I'm going to have to act like I care
about her and then we're going to get
her house.
Oh yeah, that's the good [__] right
there. Oh my god. Hell yeah. And the
water bottle shrunk off screen. That's
That's how you know that's the good
[__] Just like the pizza.
Much better. I should head back
upstairs.
He's going to be in my house. I'm
calling it.
Okay, the front door is good.
Basement door shut. Back door shut. We
good, everybody. We're good.
I mean,
I should I I should check.
Do I want to check these these places? I
I I shouldn't, but
Okay, now that now that that's out of
the way, I bet I better go to bed. I got
a big day tomorrow. Grandma's dead.
No, old man. Wherever you are,
see I if he is in the house, I'm not
going to like act like I he's the anime.
I'm I'm going to want to like, you know,
like act like he's my friend because
clearly he's not riding the head.
Oh no. Oh no. I Oh, he is in my house.
Oh my god. What do you want? Oh no. Oh
hell no. I don't like I don't like that
walk. I don't like that one. Bibm.
What do you want? No. No. No. Go. Stop.
Stop. Get away from me. Get away. OH MY
GOD. NO. GET OUT THE DOOR, MAMA.
MAMA. This is the last time mama's
leaving me home alone. I'm not I'm not
dealing with this [__] next
Halloween. Oh my god. Oh. Oh [__]
What the [__]
It's that old guy from earlier. He's in
my house. You think he thought I was
asleep?
Press A to escape the house
or D to hide.
Can I do a poll?
Hold on, [__] I'm doing a poll cuz I
don't know if there's two endings.
Okay, [__] Let's see what we do. Do I
fight for my life or do I have
God? I You You really think I can I You
think I can fight for my life and win?
I'm a 14y old [__] That guy was like
60. What could I possibly do?
Exactly.
Well,
corn yourself in the closet instead of
attaining freedom. Duh.
I mean, that would that might be the
smartest decision.
Ha. There's no time. That's what I'm
thinking. Joe 38548. Nothing is nothing
worth in this place. That is true.
Grandma's going to die. I'm probably
going to get get in her soon. You're
faster. Moon five alive. You're right.
I'm faster. I I can haul ass. I might be
a [__] but dear God, can I run?
Dear God, Kevin, get get out of here. I
need to get out of this house now before
the creep notices me. I need to run to
my neighbor for help. I thought I
thought that was my neighbor the entire
time. I guess not. W neighbor.
Oh, hold on. Before I I just realized
something. Before like I I do anything
else, I got I got to show you guys
something really cool. Like Okay, you
see like my bottom model. Look at this.
Look at that. Oh my god, I'm so cute.
Look at that. I've got ears and a tail.
I don't know how I just I I don't know
how I just like forgot about that. But
like look, isn't that cool? Look at
that. And like when I blink, look at my
ears.
Isn't that cute a shark? Hell yeah. Look
at that.
I I might need to get the ears changed
because it's like I I think the person
made them fox ears even though I asked
for mink ears, but it's like look at
that. I want them to be smaller because
you know bottle beef from Sakon is a
mink. Look at that.
Okay. Okay. Back to the game. I need to
put my I need to hold on my money
because I'm hoping like if I hold up my
money, the old man will like look at me
and and be jealous of like just HOW
[__] OH NO. Are you kidding me? No.
Did he get me? He grabbed me.
Did I lose the game? You got caught
again. Yes. I want to go again.
1:30 a.m.
All you [__] who said to escape, I'm
holding all of you accountable for that
[__]
I got to go get W again because of you
That's chat's fault. That is not my
fault. I wanted YOU TO HIDE. I WANTED TO
HIDE in the closet at just like just
like that other [__] said
because sometimes like
You know, like sometimes it's Hold on.
Is he
Okay, I'm just going I'm just going to
get the water. Okay. Damn. Okay, so he
was hiding hiding in the basement cuz
that's where he grabbed me. Okay. [__]
Okay. So,
I don't think there's any other place
that I could hide. I There's no other
place that I I could like escape unless
I can climb through a window, but I
don't know if I can do that. So I think
at least for right now the only option
we have is to have
much better.
Hell yeah.
Moon fall off. I'll take the blame
because I convinced him. Yeah. Yeah. I
blame you. May the weirdo hide. Yeah.
Yeah. You're right. I'm going to hide. I
should head back upstairs.
Okay, weird old old man.
I know you're in the house. I'm gonna
try to escape again. I'm not going to
hide. Just so you know. Just so you
know,
I am going to close the door behind me
because like that that that does uh that
does ease my fears just a little bit
knowing that he has to open the door.
Actually, [__] I should have just
opened the door. It's almost worse now
because now now I'm just waiting for for
him to come in.
Can I go out the door?
[__] Maybe if I went out the back door,
could I have escaped? Oh [__] he is
here. Oh [__]
Are you Pania? What does that mean?
Buttercotch, can I please have the
money? I was kicked out for being gay. I
mean,
no, you're you're on your own. I'm I'm
sorry. Hey, T. My partner was wondering
if you're going to be more cocoa pomel.
Too many thing said too many things.
Yeah, maybe. I don't know. I don't give
a [__] Imp. No. No, we're not doing
that. Aquamarine, we're not doing that.
Get out of here.
mods. Send him to the doodlebs. Two of
us. You know what'll happen? It's the
old guy from earlier. He's in my house.
He thought I was asleep.
Okay, we're hiding. We're hiding in the
closet.
[__] what? Why are you hiding under
the bed? Why? Literally, why? You know
what? He was just here. He knows he just
saw me in bed. Oh no.
He's going to grab me. He's going to
grab me and pull me out.
Well, you kiddo.
I don't like how you call me kiddo. I've
got some treats for you. Yeah, that'll
get me to come out. I've got the
chocolate bar and a bag of candy. See,
that almost got me because when I was in
the basement, I wanted to take that.
That's That's a tempting offer. If I
didn't know that he attacked me like the
other timeline, I I might have taken it
if if we're being honest. Like, I'm not
even kidding up in this [__]
Is he gone?
Am I free? Am I free up in this [__]
He is a pro. Billy Nomates. He is a pro.
He almost got my ass. Not even kidding.
Police. Am I free?
Oh [__]
You've never felt so relieved to hear
the sound of sirens.
Turns out the man across the street had
been awake for a while. He could sleep.
He couldn't sleep, so he was sitting by
the window just watching the
neighborhood. Your parents had told him
they'd be gone for the whole night and
asked him to keep an eye on the place.
MVP neighbor. MVP up in this [__] You
always been creeped a little a little
creeped out by him the way he just
stared too long. But tonight he noticed
something strange. He saw movement
inside your house. At first he thought
it was you. Maybe getting a drink or
heading upstairs. But when he saw a
second figure move behind you, he knew
something was wrong. He called the
police right away. By the time they
arrived, the old man had already been in
your house for a while. How long was he
in my house?
for a while.
You've Well, I did find the candy like
right when I was going to bed, so it had
been before that. You've never liked
that neighbor. But tonight, he saved
your life. THAT'S WHAT I'M TALKING
ABOUT.
They captured the old man quickly and
late later you learned he was an escaped
patient from a nearby
secure facility. I'm not going to lie,
everybody in this neighborhood was
weird. That does not surprise me that we
are living right next to like a mental
institution. He wasn't out to harm
anyone specifically. Yeah, he was.
He He tried lingu with candy. You But
you were in real danger.
I mean, he was he was out for me
specifically. You've been saved.
Other ending.
It's probably the share we already got.
We did it everyone. We Our neighbor
wasn't on the registry.
We did it, everyone.
We did it.
Can we get some W's in the chat for the
neighbor? I thought he was on the
registry, but he he's such a pretty cool
dude.
Guess you Oh, wait. What? Joe 38548
says, "Guess you got escape for the
other other ending." I don't think you
can escape. Honest to God, dead ass. I
don't think you can. Like that [__] was
was like right outside. He's at the
bottom of the stairs. Like what can you
do except for climb out the window?
Yeah, I'm not going I'm not going to
this game cuz I don't think this game I
think this is two endings.
Billy no mate 7100 says why did he know
[__] was going down though? I I think he
might be on the registry anyway.
Honestly, yeah, I am 14. Well, no. My
mom my mama told him to like watch the
house.
I'm still saying w neighbor. He maybe
he's on the register. He's saying my ass
today. I don't I don't give a [__] The
other ending is you get grabbed and
touched says completely flawless. I mean
I mean Yeah. Yeah. Mex
Finn Cannon. And I love Finn. He he g
says, "Give the old man a $25 Robux card
and maybe you'll be good." Honestly.
Yeah. Yeah. That's what I'm talking
about.
You barely even debuted. I know.
Honestly, I thought this could be a much
longer game than it actually was. Like,
cuz I saw I saw I was going to play it
for like an hour or two. Like, this
ended up being like maybe 40 40 or 50
minutes. And that's me being generous.
May maybe it was like only 30 minutes. I
don't know. Play dumb dumb. You guys
have long names. Dumb. Dumb.
Why? Yo 3185 says play D. I'm going to
I'm going to I just need to pick a short
game like this so that like you know I I
I know how streaming works and now that
I know I'm planning on playing D or
Animal Hospital or some [__] I don't
know. You're too good at games says
Troll Gi. I know. I know. I am. I know.
Hold on. Let me put my back on my ears
cuz I'm I'm sexy with them. Are they
back on? Okay. Yeah.
Look at Look how sexy I am. Look at
that. I'm so sexy. Oh my god. That's
what happens when you when you when you
pick like a bottle be avatar. I paid
2,000 bucks for this. I think I told you
guys that. It's I'm never making this
money back. Not even kidding. Like I
like with how with all my videos being
demonetized, I am never making any of
this [__] back. Oh my god. I know the
model's fire. Thanks.
Okay, hold on, [__] I might stream
again extremely soon. Maybe even in a
few hours. I don't know. I just like I
don't know what's going to happen like
to the stream. I just need to like end
it and like save it
and just see what happen.
Zazilson
says, "Yo, which tamer's brother are
you?"
I mean,
bye everyone. Thanks for tuning in to my
very first stream
and and yeah, Nat, love you. Love love
you. Love you.